Guide to the "How I Write" Podcast, Records SC1291
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiovisual Materials
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_018; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Rosaldo, undated; 6_019; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_020; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_021; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_022; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - unlabeled, undated; 6_023; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Woloch, undated; 6_024; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Frederickson, undated; 6_025; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Sapolsky, undated; 6_026; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Abernethy, undated; 6_027; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Penelope Eckert, undated; 6_028; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Middlebrook, undated; 6_029; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - McLennan, undated; 6_030; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - David Henry Hwang, 2007 Feb 13; 7_001; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 7)
  - the Stanford Daily, 2008 Jan 23; 7_002; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 7)
  - program, 2007 Nov 1; 7_003; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, undated; 7_004; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, undated; 7_005; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 7)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25; 7_006; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - John Rickford, 2002 Apr 24; 7_007; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Paula Moya, 2004 Feb 3; 7_008A; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Penny Eckert, 2003 May 22; 7_008B; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Debra Satz, 2004 Mar 3; 7_009; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - John Rickford, 2002 Apr 24; 7_010; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Terry Karl tape 1, 2004 Oct 26; 7_011; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Renato Rosalto tape 1, 2002 Apr 17; 7_012; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Zach tape 2 of 2, 2008 Apr 17; 7_013; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Graduate dissertations, 2002 Dec 4; 7_014; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Paul Robinson tape 2, 2002 May 15; 7_015; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Jones lectures, 2006 Feb 15; 7_016; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Alex Woloch, 2002 Mar 6; 7_017; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Woloch tape 2, 2002 Mar 6; 7_018; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, 2009 Nov 11; 7_019; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - tape #1, 2007 Oct 23; 7_020; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, 2009 Feb 11; 7_021; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Graduate dissertations, 2002 Dec 4; 7_022; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - tape 1 of 1, 2008 Oct 14; 7_023; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Steve Zipperstein, 2005 Apr 21; 7_024; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - PWR faculty, 2005 Jan 27; 7_025; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - 1 of 2, 2009 Jan 21; 7_026; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, undated; 7_027; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Tape 1 of 1, 2008 Oct 5; 7_028; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Shelly Fisher Fishkin, 2005 May 12; 7_029; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - R. Sapolsky, undated; 7_030; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Eavan Boland, 2004 Oct 13; 7_031; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Amy Freid, 2006 Oct 25; 7_032; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Estelle Freedman, 2003 Oct 29; 7_033; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Richard Rorty, 2004 Nov 9; 7_034; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Scotty, undated; 7_035; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Hazel Markus, 2005 Nov 8; 7_036; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Diane Middlebrook, undated; 7_037; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - President Hennessy, 2004 Apr 13; 7_038; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, 2009 Jan 21; 7_039; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, 2009 Feb 11; 7_040; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - tape 2 of 2, 2007 Nov 11; 7_041; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - VIP interviews, 2007 Feb 13; 7_042; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, 2007 May 2; 7_043; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Renato Rosaldo Tape 2, 2002 Apr 17; 7_044; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Terry Karl tape 2, 2004 Oct 26; 7_045; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Debra Satz, 2004 Mar 3; 7_046; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Terry Root, 2008 Feb 5; 7_047; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, undated; 7_048; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, undated; 7_049; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - George Fredrickson, 2003 May 8; 7_050; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Harry Elam, 2004 Apr 28; 7_051; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Diane Middlebrook tape 2, undated; 7_052; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Claude Steele, 2004 Feb 19; 7_053; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Robinson tape 1, 2002 May 15; 7_054; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Richard Miller, 2008 Apr 29; 7_055; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Andrea Lunsford, 2003 Jan 16; 7_056; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Paula Ebron part 2, 2006 Oct 10; 7_057; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - John Bravman 2, 2003 Jan 28; 7_058; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - John Bravman 1, 2003 Jan 28; 7_059; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, 2008 Apr 30; 7_060; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Paulla Ebron part 1, 2006 Oct 10; 7_061; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Troy Jollimore, 2007 Apr 25; 7_062; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Richard T Ford, 2009 Apr 16; 7_063; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - L. Roberts tape 2, 2002 Jan 30; 7_064; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - L. Roberts tape 1, 2002 Jan 30; 7_065; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Arnold Rompers, 2007 May 21; 7_066; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Eric Roberts, undated; 7_067; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb; 7_068; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Sianne Ngai tape 1, 2002 Jun 5; 7_069; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Abernethy, 2002 Feb 13; 7_070; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - David Rasch, 2003 Nov 17; 7_071; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Penelope Eckert, undated; 7_072; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Rob Reich, 2009 Apr 9; 7_073; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Sianne Ngai tape 2, 2002 Jun 5; 7_074; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Zach tape 1 of 2, 2008 Apr 17; 7_075; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Joel Beinin, 2007 Jan 17; 7_076; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 2007 May 21; 7_077; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - David Brady, 2005 Jan 13; 7_078; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Marjorie Perloff, 2006 May 3; 7_079; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Abernethy, 2002 Feb 13; 7_080; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Donald Kennedy, 2005 Feb 23; 7_081; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Barr, 2003 Nov 6; 7_082; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - unlabeled, 2007 Nov 14; 7_083; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - David Kennedy, 2005 Oct 26; 7_084; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 7)
  - Bill Guttentag, 2012 Feb 9; 8_001; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Marilyn Yalom, 2014 Feb 19; 8_002; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Marilyn Yalom, 2014 Feb 19; 8_003; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Abraham Verghese, 2011 May 4; 8_004; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Abbas Milani, 2011 Oct 26; 8_005; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Adam Johnson, 2012 Oct 23; 8_006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Susan Krieger, 2012 Apr 25; 8_007; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Susan Krieger, 2012 Apr 25; 8_008; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2007 Oct 23; 8_009; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Solnit, 2010 Apr 29; 8_010; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Solnit, 2010 Apr 29; 8_011; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 8_012; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2007 Oct 23; 8_013; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Victor L. Wooten, undated; 8_014; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Anne Firth Murray, 2006 Jan 25; 8_015; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Victor L. Wooten, 2010 May 15; 8_016; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2008 Apr 30; 8_017; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2008 Apr 30; 8_018; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2008 Apr 17; 8_019; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2008 Apr 17; 8_020; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Troy Jollimore, undated; 8_021; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Philip Taubman, 2009 Nov 11; 8_022; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 8_023; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 8_024; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Philip Taubman, 2009 Nov 11; 8_025; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rob Reich, 2009 Apr 9; 8_026; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Gwyneth Lewis, 2010 Mar 8; 8_027; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Gwyneth Lewis, 2010 Mar 8; 8_028; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Leonard Sasskind, 2007 May 2; 8_029; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2007 May 2; 8_030; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Peter Stansky, 2010 Nov 9; 8_031; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2008 Jan 21; 8_032; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2008 Jan 21; 8_033; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Richard Thompson Ford, 2009 Apr 16; 8_034; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Richard Thompson Ford, 2009 Apr 16; 8_035; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 5; 8_036; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Nancy Etchemendy, 2008 Nov 5; 8_037; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - David Henry Hwang with Hilton Obenzinger, 2007 Feb 13; 8_038; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Arnold Rampersad tape 1 of 2, 2007 May 21; 8_039; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Arnold Rampersad tape 2 of 2, 2007 May 21; 8_040; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Arnold Rampersad tape 2 of 2, 2007 May 21; 8_041; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Arnold Rampersad tape 1 of 2, 2007 May 21; 8_042; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2007 Nov 1; 8_043; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - A Conversation with Thomas Hare and Hilton Obenzinger, 2012 May 14; 8_044; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Stanford daily, 2008 Jan 23; 8_045; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Stanford daily, 2008 Jan 23; 8_046; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, 2007 Nov 1; 8_047; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Professor Ramon Saldivar, 2007 Nov 14; 8_048; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 8_049; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Dr. Terry Root, 2008 Feb 4; 8_050; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 8_051; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Richard Zare, 2008 Oct 14; 8_052; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 8_053; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 8_054; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 8_055; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rob Reich, 2009 Apr 9; 8_056; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Troy Jollimore, undated; 8_057; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Hazel Markus, 2005 Nov 8; 8_058; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - David Rasch, 2003 Nov 7; 8_059; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, undated; 8_060; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - PWR faculty, 2005 Jan 27; 8_061; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Nancy Packer, undated; 8_062; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, undated; 8_063; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, undated; 8_064; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - unlabeled, undated; 8_065; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 8_066; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Valerie Miner, 2008 Apr 30; 8_067; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Valerie Miner, 2008 Apr 30; 8_068; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Valerie Miner, 2008 Apr 30; 8_069; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Valerie Miner, 2008 Apr 30; 8_070; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Valerie Miner, 2008 Apr 30; 8_071; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Valerie Miner, 2008 Apr 30; 8_072; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Valerie Miner, 2008 Apr 30; 8_073; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Richard Rorty, 2004 Nov 9; 8_074; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Debra Satz, 2004 Mar 3; 8_075; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Debra Satz tape 2 audio, 2004 Mar 3; 8_076; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Andrea Lunsford, 2003 Jan 16; 8_077; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_078; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_079; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_080; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_081; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_082; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_083; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Philip Taubman, undated; 8_084; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Philip Taubman, undated; 8_085; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Philip Taubman, undated; 8_086; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Philip Taubman, undated; 8_087; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Jones lectures, 2006 Feb 15; 8_088; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - John Bravman (audio), 2003 Jan 28; 8_089; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Prof. Terry Castle, 2009 Feb 11; 8_090; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_091; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Rebecca Slayton, 2009 Jan 21; 8_092; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Eric Roberts, undated; 8_093; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - L. Roberts, 2002 Jan 30; 8_094; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Fred Turner, 2007 Feb 7; 8_095; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_096; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_097; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_098; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_099; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_100; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_101; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_102; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - JoAnne Akalanitis Jim Leverett, 2007 Nov 1; 8_103; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)